rilon **Halili**

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

St. 164 No. 12 Mala Recica, Tetovo, North Macedonia

□ (+389) 70-462-322 | ▼drilon.halili@qmail.com | ★www.drilonhalili.live | @drilonhalili | mdrilonhalili



Summary_

I'm Drilon, a 31 year old self-taught Frontend Developer, currently living in Tetovo. I always want to learn JS and create websites, so in 2020 I decided to take Frontend course at "Code Academy" in Skopje and after 9 months I have graduated as a Frontend Web Developer. I'm hard working, super curious, passionate, committed and a fast learner!

Work Experience _

Tetovo, N. Macedonia Freelancer

Frontend Web Developer

· Working as a React Developer for a project that provides a video-chat by connecting the customer with the client.

SLS-Solutions Tetovo, N. Macedonia

Web Developer Jun. 2019 - May. 2021

• Developed several websites using HTML, CSS and WordPress on the freelancing regime

Ecolog International FZE

Stock Controller / Operation Coordinator

Central African Republic Jun. 2016 - Jun. 2019

May. 2021 - Present

Ready to organize the team and be responsible for the dayay operations of the warehouse and department. Records purchases, maintains database, performs physical count of inventory, and reconciles actual stock count to computer-generated reports, Coordinating the shipment of goods from the warehouse. Working with Operations Manager to provide financial analysis, forecasting, assistance with budget preparation, cost control and performance to budget, maintain budget file.

Tetovo, N.Macedonia SLS-Solutions

Web Developer Jul. 2014 - Jun. 2016

• Developed several websites using HTML, CSS and Wordpress

Education _____

Code Academy

CERTIFIED FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Skopje, North Macedonia

• Completed successfully the Front-End Development Academy

State University of Tetovo

B.S. IN FINANCE AND ACCOUNTING

· Graduated economist in accounting, finance and banking division

Tetovo, North Macedonia

Oct. 2011 - June. 2014

Jun. 2020 - Feb. 2021

Skills

Technical skills:

Programming Languages: TypeScript, JavaScript, JQuery, CSS3, HTML5

Libraries & Frameworks: React.js, Next.js, Redux, Flux, Storybook, Gatsby, Styled-components, Bootstrap, Ant Design, Tailwind,

Performance Testing Frameworks: Mocha, Jest, Enzyme

Tools and Platforms: Babel, Webpack, NPM/Yarn, GIT, Sass / Less, Firebase, Sanity, Twilio, AJAX, Web-socket, Graphql, AWS, Clerk,

Projects

React - netflix

REACT - REDUX - FIREBASE - FORMIK - REACT QUERY - TAILWIND - JEST

A clone of Netflix where you need to create a user, save your favorite movies and see the movie details.

Video-chat application

NEXT JS - TWILIO - FIREBASE - TYPESCRIPT - JEST

Video chat one ore more participants, share their screen, login form, etc.

My portfolio

NEXT JS - TAILWIND - EMAILJS - JEST - FORMIK

Portfolio project that tells about me and my projects.